Guide to the Columbia Unoversity Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Arranged Files
  - Schmidt, Huber (Box 203)
  - Schmidt, Louis Bernard (Box 203)
  - Schmidt, Nathaniel (Box 203)
  - Schmidt, Robert Morell (Box 203)
  - Schn (Box 204)
  - Schneider, Herbert Wallace (Box 204)
  - Schneider, Jesse (Box 204)
  - Schneider, Louis (Box 204)
  - Schnicker, Oscar Charles (Box 204)
  - Scho. (Box 204)
  - Schoenfeld (Box 204)
  - Schoenrich, Otto (Box 204)
  - Schoeps, Hans Joachim (Box 204)
  - Schoff, Leonard Hastings (Box 204)
  - Schorr, Justin (Box 204)
  - Schr. (Box 204)
  - Schrader, Franz (Box 204)
  - Schrage, Robert W. (Box 204)
  - Schreiber, Sara Etta (Box 204)
  - Schroeder, Elinor Marie (Box 204)
  - Schub. (Box 205)
  - Schul. (Box 205)
  - Schuyler, Montgomery (Box 205)
  - Schuyler, Robert Livingston (Box 205)
  - Schw. (Box 205)
  - Schwarz, Osias L. (Box 205)
  - Schwarz, Sanford (Box 205)
  - Schwarzenberg, Adolph, 10th Prince zu (Box 205)
  - Schwebel, Milton (Box 205)
  - Schwebel, Stephen M. (Box 205)
  - Schweppe, Emma (Box 205)
  - Schyberg, Frederik, Evie Allison Allen, & Gay Wilson Allen (Box 205)
  - Sci - Scott, F. (Box 205)
  - The scientific spirit and democratic faith (Box 205)
  - Scott, Ernest Findlay (Box 205)
  - Scott, J. - Scu (Box 206)
  - Scott, J Brown (Box 206)
  - Scott, John Anthony (Box 206)
  - Scott, Nathan A. (Box 206)
  - Sea. (Box 206)
  - Seaman, Richard M. (Box 206)
  - Sears, Laurence (Box 206)
  - Seaver, Charles H. (Box 206)
  - Sec - Seg (Box 206)
  - Secor, Walter Todd. (Box 206)
  - Seegay, S.C. (Box 206)
  - Seesholtz, Anna Groh (Box 206)
  - Sefa, Ibrahim (Box 206)
  - Serge, Angelo (Box 206)
  - Sei. (Box 206)
  - Sel. (Box 206)
  - Seligman, Edwin Robert Anderson (Box 206)
  - Selivanova, Nina Nikolaevna (Box 206)
  - Selmer, Carl (Box 206)
  - Sen. (Box 207)
  - Sendry, Alfred (Box 207)
  - Senior, Clarence (Box 207)
  - Ser - Sey (Box 207)
  - Sereni, Angelo Piero (Box 207)
  - Sergio, Arturo (Box 207)
  - Seris, Hoinero (Box 207)
  - Serlio, Sebastiano (Box 207)
  - Setton, Kenneth Meyer (Box 207)
  - Sewny, Vahan Dicran (Box 207)
  - Sforza, Carlo, Count (Box 207)
  - Sforza, Guido, Count (Box 207)
  - Shabad, Theodore (Box 208)
  - Shac - Sham (Box 208)
  - Shafer, Boyd Carlisle & Carol L. (Box 208)
  - Shahan, Ewing Pope (Box 208)
  - Shanahan, William Oswald (Box 208)
  - Shallcross, Ruth Enalda (Box 208)
  - Shan - Shap (Box 208)
  - Shand, James (Box 208)
  - Shapiro, Eli (Box 208)
  - Shar. (Box 208)
  - Sharpe, Charles Farquharson Stewart (Box 208)
  - Shaw - Shay (Box 208)
  - Shaw, Albert (Box 208)
  - Shaw, Plato Ernest (Box 208)
  - Shaw, Ralph Robert (Box 208)
  - Shaw, Theodore (Box 208)
  - Shaw, Wilfred B. (Box 208)
  - Shea - Shei. (Box 209)
  - Shears, Lainbert Armour (Box 209)
  - Shel - Shep (Box 209)
  - Sheldon, Wilmon Henry (Box 209)
  - Shenton, Herbert Newhard (Box 209)
  - Shepherd, William Robert (Box 209)
  - Sher. (Box 209)
  - Sherman, Ellen Burns (Box 209)
  - Sherman, H. Lancey (Box 209)
  - Sherman, Henry Clapp (Box 209)
  - Sherman, Marsdon Alexander (Box 209)
  - Sherwood, Eleanor P. (Box 209)
  - Shi. (Box 210)
  - Shientag, Bernard Lloyd (Box 210)
  - Shipley, Joseph T. (Box 210)
  - Shlakman, Vera (Box 210)
  - Sho - Shot. (Box 210)
  - Shoemaker, Ervin C. (Box 210)
  - Shoemaker, Francis (Box 210)
  - Short, Howard Elmo (Box 210)
  - Shotwell, James Tomson (l) (Box 210)
  - Shotwell, James Tomson (2) (Box 211)
  - Shoup, Carl Sumner (Box 211)
  - Shr - Shy (Box 211)
  - Shridharani, Krishnalal & Theodore Abel (Box 211)
  - Shulim, Joseph Isidore (Box 211)
  - Shumiatcher, Morris C. (Box 211)
  - Shuster, George Nauman (Box 211)
  - Shute, Clarence William (Box 211)
  - Shwartzman, Gregory (Box 211)
  - Sib - Sie (Box 211)
  - Sibley, Agnes Marie (Box 211)
  - Sickels, Eleanor Maria (Box 211)
  - Sievers, Allen Morris (Box 211)
  - Siepmann, Charles A. (Box 211)
  - Sil. (Box 211)
  - Silver, Rollo G. (Box 211)
  - Sime - Simk (Box 212)
  - Simkhovitch, Vladimir Grigorievitch (Box 212)
  - Simm - Sims (Box 212)
  - Simmons, Ernest Joseph (Box 212)
  - Simmons, Leo W. (Box 212)
  - Simon, Andre L. (Box 212)
  - Simons, J.B. (Box 212)
  - Simpson, Cuthbert Aikman (Box 212)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord (Box 212)
  - Simutis, Anicetas (Box 212)
  - Sin - Siw (Box 212)
  - Sinclair, J.G. (Box 212)
  - Singer, Edgar Arthur (Box 212)
  - Sk. (Box 212)
  - Skidmore, College Anniversary Publication (Box 212)
  - Sla - Sle (Box 212)
  - Slavon, Samuel Richard (Box 212)
  - Slo - Sly (Box 212)
  - Sma - Smir (Box 213)
  - Smallwood, William Martin (Box 213)
  - Smart, Harold R. (Box 213)
  - Smiley, Charles Newton (Box 213)
  - Smiley, Joseph R. (Box 213)
  - Smith, A. - Smith H. (Box 213)
  - Smith, Bunnie Othanel (Box 213)
  - Smith, Bruce (Box 213)
  - Smith, Elva S. (Box 213)
  - Smith, Florence Mary (Box 213)
  - Smith, Franklin Abbott (Box 213)
  - Smith., Horatio Elwin (Box 213)
  - Smith, J. - Smo. (Box 214)
  - Smith, Joseph Henry (Box 214)
  - Smith, Joseph Russell (Box 214)
  - Smith, Marian Wesley (Box 214)
  - Smith, Maxwell A. (Box 214)
  - Smith, Munroe (Box 214)
  - Smith, Newlin Russell (Box 214)
  - Smith, R. Collin (Box 214)
  - Smith, Robert Metcalf (Box 214)
  - Smith, Russell Gordon (Box 214)
  - Smith, Sara Rector (Box 214)
  - Smith, Thomas Russell (Box 214)
  - Smith, Thomas Vernor & Robert A. Taft (Box 214)
  - Sn. (Box 215)
  - Snyder, Louis L. (Box 215)
  - Snyder, Richard Canton (Box 215)
  - Snyder, Thomas E. (Box 215)
  - Sob - Sok (Box 215)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 215)
  - Soibelman, Doris (Box 215)
  - Sol - Som (Box 215)
  - Son - Sor (Box 215)
  - Sonne, Niels Henry (Box 215)
  - Sonneborn, Hilton Burnside Paul Francis (Box 215)
  - Sou - Soz (Box 215)
  - Souleyman, Elizabeth V. (Box 215)
  - Southard, Frank Allan (Box 215)
  - Southworth, James Granville (Box 215)
  - The Southworth Press (Portland, Me.) (Box 215)
  - Spa. (Box 216)
  - Spanheimer, Sr, M. Edmund (Box 216)
  - Spaulding, Ernest Wilder (Box 216)
  - Spe. (Box 216)
  - Spearman, Diana (Box 216)
  - Speck, Frank Gouldsmith (Box 216)
  - Spector, Ivar (Box 216)
  - Spencer, Coninne (Box 216)
  - Spencer, Ivor D. (Box 216)
  - Spencer, Theodore & Mark Van Doren (Box 216)
  - Speranza, Gino Charles & Florence Colgate Speranza (Box 216)
  - Spero, Herbert (Box 216)
  - Spero, Sterling Denhard & Abram L. Harris (Box 216)
  - Spi - Spo (Box 216)
  - Spiegel, Henry William (Box 216)
  - Spiers, Alexander G.H,, Isidore Henry Bowles Spiers, & Frederick Barry (Box 216)
  - Spingarn, Joel Elias (Box 216)
  - Spinka, Matthew (Box 216)
  - Spitsbergen, H. E. (Box 216)
  - Spr-Sq (Box 217)
  - Sprietsma, Cargill (Box 217)
  - Spring, Agnes Wright (Box 217)
  - Sprott, S. Ernest (Box 217)
  - Stac. (Box 217)
  - Staf - Stam (Box 217)
  - Stahl, William Harris (Box 217)
  - Stan - Stap (Box 217)
  - Stanley, Oma (Box 217)
  - Stanoyevich, Milivoy Stoyan (Box 217)
  - Star. (Box 217)
  - Starkey, Otis Paul (Box 217)
  - Starr, Nathan Comfort (Box 217)
  - Stavrianos, L. S. (Box 217)
  - Stead, Rexford (Box 217)
  - Stearns, Anna (Box 217)
  - Stearns, Marshall Winslow (Box 217)
  - Stebbins, George Ledyard (Box 218)
  - Stebbins, Lucy Poate & Richard Poate Stebbins (Box 218)
  - Stec - Steg (Box 218)
  - Stedman, Murray Salisbury & Susan Winter Stedman (Box 218)
  - Steed, Henry Wickham (Box 218)
  - Steeves, Edna Leake (Box 218)
  - Steeves, Harrison Ross (Box 218)
  - Steffler, Clarence William (Box 218)
  - Stei. (Box 219)
  - Steigman, Benjamin M. (Box 219)
  - Stein, Charles W. (Box 219)
  - Steinberg, Moses (Box 219)
  - Stel - Step (Box 219)
  - Stenius, Arthur (Box 219)
  - Stephens, John Lloyd (Box 219)
  - Stephens, Waldo Emerson (Box 219)
  - Ster - Stet (Box 219)
  - Stern, Alfred (Box 219)
  - Stern, Bernhard Joseph (Box 219)
  - Stern, Fritz (Box 219)
  - Stern, Siegfried (Box 219)
  - Sterok, David (Box 219)
  - Stev. (Box 219)
  - Stevenson, David Lloyd (Box 219)
  - Stevenson, Frederic R. & Carl Feiss (Box 219)
  - Stevenson, Robert Murrell (Box 219)
  - Stew. (Box 219)
  - Stewart, Herbert Leslie (Box 219)
  - Stewart, William A. (Box 219)
  - Sti... (Box 220)
  - Stillman, Clara G. (Box 220)
  - Stillman, Leon (Box 220)
  - Stillwell, Margaret Bingham (Box 220)
  - Stirling Alexander Williamson (Box 220)
  - Stirling, Brents (Box 220)
  - Stoa - Stoh (Box 220)
  - Stockder, Archibald Herbert (Box 220)
  - Stoddard, Paul Wakelee (Box 220)
  - Stolzenberg, Bessie (Box 220)
  - Stan - Stou (Box 220)
  - Stone, Dena (Box 220)
  - Stone, Harlan Fiske (Box 220)
  - Stout, George Leslie (Box 220)
  - Stra - Stre (Box 220)
  - Strachan, James Ernest (Box 220)
  - Strathmann, Ernest Albert (Box 220)
  - Straus, Hannah Alice (Box 220)
  - Strickler, Fred (Box 220)
  - Strikes, History of (Box 220)
  - Stro - Stry (Box 221)
  - Strong, Edward W. (Box 221)
  - Strong, William Duncan; Gordon Randolph Willey; & John M. Corbett (Box 221)
  - Stroup, Herbert Hewitt (Box 221)
  - Stu - Sty (Box 221)
  - Stuart, Donald Clive (Box 221)
  - Stuerm, Francis H. (Box 221)
  - Sturdevant, Winifred (Box 221)
  - Sturgill, Walter S. (Box 221)
  - Sturnthal, Adolf Fox (Box 221)
  - Sua - Sul (Box 222)
  - Sum-Sup (Box 222)
  - Sumberg, Samuel Leslie (Box 222)
  - Summers, Montague (Box 222)
  - Suppan, A. A. (Box 222)
  - Sut. (Box 222)
  - Sutcliffe, Emerson Grant (Box 222)
  - Sutherland, George (Box 222)
  - Sutherland, Stella Helen (Box 222)
  - Swa. (Box 222)
  - Swain, Barbara (Box 222)
  - Swann, Harvey Julian (Box 222)
  - Swayzee, Cleon Oliphant (Box 222)
  - Swe. (Box 222)
  - Swenarton, Jane J. (Box 222)
  - Swi. (Box 222)
  - Swift, Emerson Howland (Box 222)
  - Swift, Jonathan, 1667-l745 (Box 222)
  - Swiggett, Howard (Box 222)
  - Swindler, William Dinley (Box 222)
  - Sy .- Sz (Box 223)
  - Sylvania, Lena Eyelyn V. (Box 223)
  - Symons, Percival Mallon (Box 223)
  - Symonds, Richard (Box 223)
  - Syrett, H Coffin (Box 223)
  - Szladits, Lola L. (Box 223)
  - Tab - Tam (Box 223)
  - Tabrizi, Saiyid Ahmad Kasrawi (Box 223)
  - Taffel, Abram (Box 223)
  - Taft, William Howard (Box 223)
  - Taggart, Joseph H. (Box 223)
  - Tamir, Max M. (Box 223)
  - Tan - Tau (Box 223)
  - Tandy, Jennette Reid (Box 223)
  - Tannenbaum, Frank (Box 223)
  - Tannenbaum, Samuel Aaron (Box 223)
  - Tappan, Paul Wilbur (Box 223)
  - Taus, Esther Rogoff (Box 223)
  - Tav (Box 224)
  - Tavenner, Eugene (Box 224)
  - Taylor (Box 224)
  - Taylor, Francis Henry (Box 224)
  - Taylor, Horace (Box 224)
  - Taylor, John Tinnon (Box 224)
  - Taylor, Joseph Russell (Box 224)
  - Taylor, Rupert (Box 224)
  - Taylor, William Lonsdale (Tayler?) (Box 224)
  - Tea - Ten (Box 224)
  - Teleky, Ludwig (Box 224)
  - Temple, Sydney A., Jr. (Box 224)
  - Tennant, Peter Frank Dalrymple (Box 224)
  - Ter - Tex (Box 224)
  - Teslar, J.A. (Box 224)
  - Tha - The (Box 225)
  - Thatcher, Harold W. (Box 225)
  - Thelen, Mary Frances (Box 225)
  - There is another China (Box 225)
  - Thi - Thod (Box 225)
  - Thierry, James Francis (Box 225)
  - Thom. (Box 225)
  - Thomas (Box 225)
  - Thomas, Arthur Waldorf Spittal (Box 225)
  - Thomas, Bernadette (Box 225)
  - Thomas, Eleanor Walter (Box 225)
  - Thomas, Mary Edith (Box 225)
  - Thomas, Milton Halsey (Box 225)
  - Thomas, Sidney (Box 225)
  - Thompson (Box 226)
  - Thompson, Daniel Garrison Brinton (Box 226)
  - Thompson, Eleanor Wolf (Box 226)
  - Thompson, Laura (Box 226)
  - Thompson, Victor Alexander (Box 226)
  - Thompson, Walter (Box 226)
  - Thomson (Box 226)
  - Thomson, James, l700-1748 (Box 226)
  - Thor (Box 226)
  - Thorndike, Ashley Horace (Box 226)
  - Thorndike, Lynn (1) (Box 226)
  - Thorndike, Lynn (2) (Box 227)
  - Thornton, Janet (Box 227)
  - Thornton, Willis (Box 227)
  - Thr. (Box 227)
  - Thrall, Miriam Mulford. H. (Box 227)
  - Thurston, Henry Winfred (Box 228)
  - Tib - Til (Box 228)
  - Tieck, Johann Ludwig, 1773-1853 (Box 228)
  - Tietze, George H. (Box 228)
  - Tilghman, Zoe A. (Box 228)
  - Tilley, Margaret C. (Box 228)
  - Tim - Tit (Box 228)
  - Tindall, William York (Box 228)
  - Tingle, W.R. (Box 228)
  - Tirrell, Sarah Rebecca (Box 228)
  - Tischler, Hans (Box 228)
  - Tob - Tol (Box 229)
  - Tobriner, Mathew O. (Box 229)
  - Todd, Henry Alfred Todd memorial volumes (Box 229)
  - Toffanin, Giuseppe (Box 229)
  - Tolles, Winton (Box 229)
  - Tolstoy Sukhotina, Countess Tatiana Lvovna (Box 229)
  - Tom - Ton (Box 229)
  - Tombs, Laurence Chalmers (Box 229)
  - Tomlinson, Laurence E. (Box 229)
  - Topazio, Virgil W. (Box 229)
  - Tor - Toz (Box 229)
  - The Torch Press (Cedar Rapids, Iowa) (Box 229)
  - Torrey, Norman Lewis (Box 229)
  - Toscanini, Walter (Box 229)
  - Toumanova, Princess Nina Andronikova (Box 229)
  - Townsend, W. Cameron (Box 229)
  - Toynbee, Arnold Joseph (Box 229)
  - Tra. (Box 230)
  - The Royal Historical Society Transylvania (Box 230)
  - Tranter, G. J. (Box 230)
  - Trattner, Ernest Robert (Box 230)
  - Travers, Seymour (Box 230)
  - Travis, James Richard (Box 230)
  - Tre - Tri (Box 230)
  - Trebein, Bertha Eleanor (Box 230)
  - Trenholme, Louise Irby (Box 230)
  - Triebel, L. A. (Box 230)
  - Trilling, Lionel (Box 230)
  - Tro-Ts (Box 230)
  - Troelston Emil S. (Box 230)
  - Troyer, Howard William (Box 230)
  - Trubetskoi, Nikolai Sergeevich (Box 230)
  - Tschan, Francis Joseph (Box 230)
  - Tschaplianski, Basilius (Box 230)
  - Tschichold., Jan (Box 230)
  - Tsurumi, Yusuke (Box 230)
  - Tuc - Tim (Box 231)
  - Tucker, Samuel Marion (Box 231)
  - Tugwell, Rexford Guy (Box 231)
  - Tur - Tuv (Box 231)
  - Turlington, Edgar (Box 231)
  - Turnbull, Eleanor L. (Box 231)
  - Tute, Sir Richard Clifford (Box 231)
  - Tuttle, Stephen (Box 231)
  - Tv - Tz (Box 231)
  - Tyler, Parker (Box 231)
  - Tyler, Royall (Box 231)
  - Ullendorff, Edward (Box 232)
  - Ulmer, Melville Jack (Box 232)
  - Ulrich, Homer (Box 232)
  - Un. (Box 232)
  - Underhill, Ruth Murray (Box 232)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific &. Cultural Organization Community studies. (Box 232)
  - UNESCO Energy in the service of man. (Box 232)
  - UNESCO Freedom and culture. (Box 232)
  - UNESCO Human rights. (Box 232)
  - UNESCO Translation project - Latin America (Box 232)
  - U.S. National bureau of standards Computation laboratory. (Box 232)
  - U.S. Navy department Office of naval research (Box 232)
  - U.S. War department Gazetteers (Box 232)
  - University of Brussels (Box 233)
  - University presses (Box 233)
  - University presses - survey (Box 233)
  - Up - Uz (Box 233)
  - Upjohn, Everard Miller (Box 233)
  - Upjohn, William Treat (Box 233)
  - Vaeth, Joseph Anthony (Box 233)
  - Vag - Val (Box 233)
  - Vail, Curtis Churchill Doughty (Box 233)
  - Valency, Maurice Jacques (Box 233)
  - Vam-Van D (Box 234)
  - Van Buren, Paul M. (Box 234)
  - Van Driel, Agnes (Box 234)
  - Van Gelder, Arthur Pine (Box 234)
  - Van Hook, LaRue (Box 234)
  - Van Ingen, Phillip (Box 234)
  - Van Kleffens, E. N. (Box 234)
  - Vann - Van R. (Box 234)
  - Van Norden, Warner M. (Box 234)
  - Vans - Vau (Box 234)
  - Van Til, Cornelius (Box 234)
  - Van Fleck, George Washington (Box 234)
  - Van Wagenen, Richard W. (Box 234)
  - Vecchio, Giorgio del (Box 234)
  - Ver (Box 234)
  - Vernadsky, George (Box 234)
  - Vernon, Raymond (Box 234)
  - Vi. (Box 234)
  - Virtue, Maxine Boord (Box 234)
  - Voe - Voo (Box 235)
  - Volgyesi, F. (Box 235)
  - Von A - Von S (Box 235)
  - Von Fritz, Kurt (Box 235)
  - Von Gronicka, Andre (Box 235)
  - Von Hentig, Hans (Box 235)
  - Von Mohrenschildt, Dimitri Sergius (Box 235)
  - Vu. (Box 235)
  - Wa. (Box 235)
  - Waas, Glenn Elwood (Box 235)
  - Wag. (Box 235)
  - Waggoner, Hyatt H. (Box 235)
  - Wagley, Charles (Box 235)
  - Wagman, Frederick Herbert (Box 235)
  - Wagner, Gunter (Box 235)
  - Wald - Walk (Box 235)
  - Wald, Haskell P. & Joseph N, Froomkin (Box 235)
  - Waldron Gloria (Box 235)
  - Waldstein, Abraham Solomon (Box 235)
  - Walker (Box 235)
  - Walker, Curtis Howe (Box 235)
  - Walker Engraving Corporation (Box 235)
  - Wallace (Box 236)
  - Wallace, Schuyler Crawford (Box 236)
  - Walli - Wallm (Box 236)
  - Wallis, Lawrence Bergmann (Box 236)
  - Wallis, Louis (Box 236)
  - Wallis, Wilson D. (Box 236)
  - Wals. (Box 236)
  - Walston, Sir Charles (Box 236)
  - Walter, Maximilian Graff (Box 236)
  - Wang, Chi-chen (Box 237)
  - Wang, Chi Kao (Box 237)
  - Wang, Ching-Chun (Box 237)
  - Wang, Ke-Chin (Box 237)
  - Wang, Kung-Ping (Box 237)
  - Warb - Ware (Box 238)
  - Warburton, Clark Abram (Box 238)
  - Ward (Box 238)
  - Ward, Charles E. (Box 238)
  - Warden, Carl John (Box 238)
  - Ware, Caroline Farrar (Box 238)
  - Ware, Edith Ellen (Box 238)
  - Ware, Louise (Box 238)
  - Warn - Wars (Box 238)
  - Warner, Aaron W. (Box 238)
  - Warner, Arthur W. (Box 238)
  - Warren, Dorothy & Marjorie (Box 238)
  - Warren, Robert Beach (Box 238)
  - Was. (Box 238)
  - Wat - Wax (Box 238)
  - Watson (Box 238)
  - Watson, Harold Francis (Box 238)
  - Wattenberg, William W. (Box 238)
  - Wea - Web (Box 239)
  - Weber, Adna Ferrin (Box 239)
  - Weber, Carl Jefferson (Box 239)
  - Weber, Kurt (Box 239)
  - Weber, Paul Carl (Box 239)
  - Weber, Thomas (Box 239)
  - Wed - Weg (Box 239)
  - Weeks, Raymond (Box 239)
  - Weim - Wein (Box 239)
  - Weindling, Ludwig (Box 239)
  - Weiner, Seymour Sidney (Box 239)
  - Weinstein, Harold R. (Box 239)
  - Weis - Weit (Box 239)
  - Weisert, John Jacob (Box 239)
  - Weic. (Box 240)
  - Welch, E. Parl (Box 240)
  - Weld, Ralph Foster (Box 240)
  - Welfare Council of New York City Series (Box 240)
  - Well-Welt (Box 241)
  - Wells, Sumner (Box 241)
  - Wells, Harry Kohlsaat (Box 241)
  - Wells, Henry Willis (Box 241)
  - Wells, Ron Vale (Box 241)
  - Wen. (Box 241)
  - Wendell, Mitchell (Box 241)
  - Wendt, Herman George "George Adams" (Box 241)
  - Wer. (Box 242)
  - Wermel, Michael Theodore (Box 242)
  - Werner, Oscar Helmuth (Box 242)
  - Wes-Wex (Box 242)
  - West, James See: Withers, Carl (Box 242)
  - Westcott, Allan F. (Box 242)
  - Westremann, William Linn; Clinton Walker Keyes; Kraemer, Casper John, Jr.; Herbert Liebesny, & Elizabeth Sayre Hasenoehrl (Box 242)
  - Westphal, Albert Charles Frederick (Box 242)
  - Whe. (Box 243)
  - Wheeler, William Morton (Box 243)
  - Whicher, George Frisbie (Box 243)
  - Whicher, George Meason (Box 243)
  - Whitaker, Albert Conser (Box 244)
  - Whitaker, Arthur Preston: Inter American Affairs (Box 237)
  - White (Box 245)
  - White, Doris Isobel (Box 245)
  - White, Lazarus & Edmund Astley Prentis See also: Prentis. (Box 245)
  - White, Melvin Irvin (Box 245)
  - White, Morton Gabriel (Box 245)
  - White, Nelson C. (Box 245)
  - Whitei - Whitf (Box 245)
  - Whiting, Gertrude (Box 245)
  - Whitm - Whitw (Box 246)
  - Whitman, Walt (Box 246)
  - Whitman, William (Box 246)
  - Wic - Wid (Box 246)
  - Wichert, Hildegarde Edith (Box 246)
  - Wie - Wig (Box 246)
  - Wieler, John William (Box 246)
  - Wiers, Paul (Box 246)
  - Wilb - Wild (Box 246)
  - Wilgus, William John (Box 246)
  - Wilkes, Benjamin Garrison (Box 247)
  - Wilkinson, Rachel Diggs (Box 247)
  - Will - Wille (Box 247)
  - Willcox, O. W. (Box 247)
  - Willey, Gordon Randolph & John M. Corbett (Box 247)
  - Willey, Basil (Box 247)
  - Willia. (Box 247)
  - Williams, Blanche Colton (Box 247)
  - Williams, Elgin (Box 247)
  - Williams, John Sharp (Box 247)
  - Williams, Judith Blow (Box 247)
  - Williams, Stanley Thomas (Box 247)
  - Williamson, Charles Clarence (Box 247)
  - Williamson, Margaretta A. (Box 247)
  - Willis (Box 248)
  - Willis, Henry Parker & John M Chapman (Box 248)
  - Willis, Parker Brown (Box 248)
  - Willoughby (Box 248)
  - Wilson, A. - Wilson, L. (Box 248)
  - Wilson, Cecile (Box 248)
  - Wilson, Charles Morrow (Box 248)
  - Wilson, Curtis (Box 248)
  - Wilson, Daniel M. (Box 248)
  - Wilson, Harold Fisher (Box 248)
  - Wilson, John Howard (Box 248)
  - Wilson, M - W. (Box 249)
  - Wilson, Margaret Barclay (Box 249)
  - Wilson, Pearl Cleveland (Box 249)
  - Wilson, Samuel, Jr. (Box 249)
  - Wilson, Stanley Kidder (Box 249)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Box 249)
  - Wimsatt, Genevieve Blanche (Box 250)
  - Win (Box 250)
  - Winch, Robert F. (Box 250)
  - Winesanker, Michael (Box 250)
  - Wingert, Paul Stover (Box 250)
  - Winslow, Earle Micajah (Box 250)
  - Wis. (Box 250)
  - Wise, George Schneiweis (Box 250)
  - Wise, Maurice Kulbert (Box 250)
  - Wismar, Adolph Louis (Box 250)
  - Wit. (Box 251)
  - Withers, Carl "James West" (Box 251)
  - Withers, William (Box 251)
  - Wittenberg, Philip (Box 251)
  - Wittmann, Erno (Box 251)
  - Wod - Wog (Box 251)
  - Woelfel, Norman (Box 251)
  - Wol - Worn (Box 252)
  - Wolfe, Martin (Box 252)
  - Wolff, Kurt H. (Box 252)
  - Wollstein, Rose Heylbut (Box 252)
  - Wolman, Leo (Box 252)
  - Wood (Box 252)
  - Wood, Alice Ida Perry (Box 252)
  - Wood, Francis Carter (Box 252)
  - Wood, Frank Higley (Box 252)
  - Wood, Margaret Mary (Box 252)
  - Wood, Mary Morton (Box 252)
  - Wood, Robert William (Box 252)
  - Wooda - Woodb (Box 252)
  - Woodberry, George Edward (Box 252)
  - Woodbridge, Frederick James Eugene (Box 252)
  - [F.J.E] Woodbridge Lecture Publication Fund (Box 252)
  - Woodbridge, George (Box 252)
  - Woods - Wool (Box 253)
  - Woodworth, Robert Sessions (Box 253)
  - Wor. (Box 253)
  - Worsley, Thomas B. (Box 253)
  - Wright (Box 253)
  - Wright, Ernest Hunter (Box 253)
  - Wright, Henry (Box 253)
  - Wright, Herbert (Box 253)
  - Wright, Ivan & Arthur M. Wolkiser (Box 253)
  - Wright, John Kirkland (Box 253)
  - Wright, Louis B. (Box 253)
  - Wright, Luella Margaret (Box 253)
  - Wright, Wilmer Cave (Box 253)
  - Wro. (Box 253)
  - Wu - Wy (Box 254)
  - Wuorinen, John Henry (Box 254)
  - Wyckoff, Viola (Box 254)
  - Wyman, Mary Alice (Box 254)
  - Wythe, George (Box 254)
  - Ya-Yi (Box 255)
  - Yang, Martin Mou-ch'un (Box 255)
  - Yarborough, Minnie Clare (Box 255)
  - Yeandle, Frederic George (Box 255)
  - Yo. (Box 255)
  - Yoder, Audrey Elizabeth (Box 255)
  - Young (Box 255)
  - Young, Bradford (Box 255)
  - Young, Sir George (Box 255)
  - Younger, Richard Davis (Box 255)
  - Za - Ze (Box 256)
  - Zahler, Helene Sara (Box 256)
  - Zanetti, Joaquin Enrique (Box 256)
  - Zarina, Xenia (Box 256)
  - Zeller, Belle (Box 256)
  - Zeydel, Edwin Herman (Box 256)
  - Zie. (Box 256)
  - Zilboorg, Gregory (Box 256)
  - Zirn. (Box 257)
  - Zimmerman, Jane Dorsey (Box 257)
  - Zink, Sidney (Box 257)
  - Ziskind, David (Box 257)
  - Znaniecki, Florian (Box 257)
  - Zo - Zu (Box 257)
  - Zouboff, Peter P. (Box 257)
  - Zubin, Joseph & Thea Stein Lewinson (Box 257)
  - Zucker, Adolf Eduard (Box 257)
- Series III: Office Files
  - General correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 258)
  - Account books, 1893-1914 (Box 259)
  - Account with Interstate Trust Company, 1929-1930 (Box 260)
  - Accounting department, 1940-1949 (Box 260)
  - Advertising, publicity, & review, 1947-1950 (Box 260)
  - Advisory Committee on Social Work Publications, 1939 -1951 (Box 260)
  - Authors' brochure, 1946 (Box 260)
  - Author's hand bound copies, 1938-1941 (Box 260)
  - Authors - misc., 1941-1947 (Box 260)
  - Bonding insurance, 1949/1950 (Box 260)
  - Book exhibits, 1934-1938 (Box 260)
  - Books - manufacturing requirements, 1933 (Box 260)
  - Bookstore, 1897-1949 (Box 260)
  - Bookstore - Social Security, 1937 (Box 261)
  - Bookstore - transfer from Lemcke & Buechner, 1921-1924 (Box 261)
  - Bookstore - union matters, 1950/1951 (Box 261)
  - Budget, 1953 (Box 261)
  - Budget, 1954 (Box 261)
  - Budget, 1955 (Box 261)
  - Cleaning - spring & fall, 1950 (Box 261)
  - College Publishers Group, 1948 (Box 261)
  - Contracts - books & bookstore, 1897-1920 (Box 261)
  - Distribution sales, 1937 (Box 261)
  - Duplicating department, 1930 (Box 261)
  - Editorial department, 1930 (Box 261)
  - Earnings, 1947 (Box 261)
  - Employee benefits, 1936-1949 (Box 261)
  - 50th Anniversary, 1942 (Box 261)